ILR School Metropolitan Office Records /4268
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Metropolitan Office Records
1971-2008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Metropolitan Office
/4268
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
8072111
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 04, 2008
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3019: ILR School Metropolitan District Selected Documents /4257: ILR School Metropolitan District Selected Files /4068: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office, Anne Nelson Papers /4089: ILR School Metropolitan District Office Additional Files /4266m: ILR School Metropolitan District Levi Strauss files /4277: ILR School Metropolitan District Trade Union Health Education Project Papers /4026: ILR School Metropolitan Office Extension Division Completed Questionnaires on Union Activity /4296: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Manuals /4296 AV: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Audio-Visual Materials
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Metropolitan Office
8072111
- Contains New York City entertainment industry material. (Box 1)
  - Semel, Rochelle. Industrial Workers of the World., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cornell 11, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Donna Zahorik, Judith Long Laws, Jacqueline Livingston, Antonia Glasse, and Charlotte Farris v. Cornell University. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Building an Active Women's Committee. folder 1, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Building an Active Women's Committee. folder 2, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Handbook for Union Staff Women, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Kopelov, Connie. Trade Union Women and Women's Rights., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Institute for Women and Work. ILR. Lighting the Torch for Labor Education., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Trade Union Women's Studies. ILR. Focus on Women Unionists. Proceedings., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bomboy, Marylee. Papers relating to Chase Program., 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Margolies, Kenneth and Pamela Henderson. ILR. Cultural Diversity Training Materials for Labor Unions., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Semel, Rochelle. Planning Manual for Coordinators of the University and College Labor Education Association's Northeast Summer School for Union Women., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Committes, Coalitions, and Networks: Making An Impact. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Pay Equity: Issue for the '80s., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - UCLEA Summer School for Union Women. Labor Education Workshop., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Taub, Laurie. Women Labor Unions. Local 342 Study., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Sanford V. Lenz Library. Dedication., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Nelson, Ann, Collector. Barbara Wertheimer Memorial, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Perspectives of the Metropolitan District, Division of Extension and Public Service NYSSILR, Cornell University, 1981-1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - ILR Strategic Planning., 1971-1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - A Commitment to Equality: One Century Later. Report of the Ad Hoc Trustee Committee on The Status of Women., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Final Report of the ILR Faculty Internal Review Committee., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Institute for Women and Work. ILR. Workshops., 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Two Photographs and a Slide made from one of them. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Cook, Alice. Women and Trade Unions in Five European Countries., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - New York State United Teachers (NYSUT)., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - ILR. Institute for Workplace Studies., 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Christopherson, Susan. Behind the Scenes: How Transformational Firms are Constructing a New International Division of Labor in Media Work, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Report of External Review Committee: Baruch-Cornell MSILR Program, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - New York City Economic Development Corporation: The NYC Economic Impact Strategy for the Arts, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Creative New York, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - The Entertainment Arts Industry in New York, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - An Assessment of the Career Counseling Needs of Performing Artists, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Economic Impact of the Arts on New York City and New York State, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 34)